Finding Aid for the S. Charles Lee papers LSC.1384
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Blueprints/Rolled Plans
  - Tower Theatre (H.L. Gumbiner), Los Angeles, 1 roll blueprints - arch., marquee; 1 roll too fragile to handle. (Box 67)
  - Tower Theatre (H.L. Gumbiner), Los Angeles, 1 roll - structural, a/c, site plan, blueprints, floor plans, sections. (Box 135)
  - Tower Theatre (H.L. Gumbiner), Los Angeles, flat box - ca. 100 folded drawings; details on trace. (Box 314)
  - Tower Theatre, (Gumbiner), 8th ' Broadway, 1926, 1 roll b-p, fragile, 10 sheets floor plans and mech. Systems. (Box 117)
  - Tubing Appliance, 10323 La Cienaga, A-8. (Box 97)
  - Unidentified Shops. (Box 43)
  - Unidentified Store (wine room). (Box 38)
  - Union Furniture Company Store, San Francisco. (Box 31)
  - Valor, 13214 Crenshaw Blvd., B-4. (Box 108)
  - Vern Theatre (Wyvernwood Theatres Incorporated), Los Angeles. (Box 51)
  - Vogue Theatre (Sheehan ' Sinks), Hollywood. (Box 78)
  - Wasco Theatre (Frank Panero), Wasco. (Box 50)
  - Whitelock, Frank L., San Bernardino. (Box 73)
    (see Bunker Hill Square)
  - Whitelock, Frank L., San Bernardino. (Box 79)
- Plans/Renderings
  - Academy Theatre (Manchester Blvd., Theatre Corp.), Inglewood (Folder 207)
  - Admiral Theatre - Stern (Julius), Hollywood (Folder 207)
  - Aero Services (Palmdale Airport), Palmdale (Folder 201)
  - Alex Theatre (Fox West Coast), Glendale (Folder 208)
  - Aller (Joseph) - Residence, Los Angeles (Folder 149)
  - Alvarado Theatre, Los Angeles (Folder 208)
  - Amado (R.S.) -Store, Los Angeles (Folder 265)
  - Ambassador Hotel (Variety Club), Los Angeles (Folder 265)
  - American Legion (American Legion Building), Culver City (Folder 266)
    Scope and Contents note
    (FRAGILE)
  - American Theatre, Newhall (Folder 192)
  - American Theatre (American Legion), Newhall (Folder 208)
  - Anaheim Theatre (Folder 209)
  - Arcade Theatre, Los Angeles (Folder 209)
  - Arden Theatre (Hanson and Zimmerman), Lynwood (Folder 210)
  - Associates Inc. Apartment building, Beverly Hills (Folder 150)
  - Associates Inc. Hotel, Beverly Hills (Folder 266)
  - Associates Inc. Residence, Burbank (Folder 150)
  - Associates Inc. Triplex, Beverly Hills (Folder 150)
  - Atkin's (Tommy) Dryv Inn Restaurant [Adkins (Wilson)] (Folder 265)
  - Babcock (L.G.) - Medical Office Building, Vernon (Folder 266)
  - Barancik apartment building (Folder 151)
  - Baron Bros. - Theatre / Office, Mitchell, South Dakota (Folder 242)
  - Bay Theatre, Los Angeles (Folder 192)
  - Bay Theatre (Leland Ford), Los Angeles (Folder 211)
  - Bay Theatre (matted rendering), Los Angeles (Folder 315)
  - Benson Building, Los Angeles (Folder 266)
  - Berkeley Theatre - Moore (Albert), Berkeley (Folder 212)
  - Berkoff (Louis) Medical Office Building, Los Angeles (Folder 267)
  - Berkoff (Louis) Theatre, Los Angeles (Folder 242)
  - Berman (Adolph) - Store, [Los Angeles] (Folder 267)
  - Beverly Fairfax Community Center Library (Folder 202)
  - Beverly Ridge Estates (Folder 151)
  - Beverly Ridge Estates sign (Folder 189)
  - Beverly Theatre (Fox West Coast), Beverly Hills (Folder 209)
  - Big Bear Theatre, Big Bear Lake (Folder 212)
  - Blackstone Building, Los Angeles (Folder 267)
  - Blumenfeld (Joseph) - apartment interior, San Francisco (Folder 152)
  - Boasberg (Albert) - Residence, Los Angeles (Folder 152)
  - Bomb shelter/Pedestrian tunnel (Folder 191)
  - Bomb shelter/Pedestrian tunnel (Folder 202)
  - Booth Theatre - Booth (Walter), Pomona (Folder 209)
  - Bowling Alley (Folder 268)
  - Broadway Garment Building Srere Corporation, Los Angeles (Folder 300)
  - Browning (Tod) - beach studio, Malibu (Folder 153)
  - Browning (Tod) - residence, Beverly Hills (Folder 153)
  - Bruce Arms - Silbert (Sam)- apartment building (Folder 180)
  - Bundy Theatre (Bourke & Baylis), Santa Monica (Folder 212)
  - Burton & Co., Los Angeles (Folder 190)
  - Caldwell residence, Los Angeles (Folder 153)
  - California Builders (El Mirador) apartment building, Los Angeles (Folder 154)
  - California Theatre (Fox West Coast), Glendale (Folder 213)
  - Calvi (E.S.)Theatre, Lennox (Folder 242)
  - Camrose Apartments (Phillips)- apartment building, Hollywood (Folder 175)
  - Capitol Theatre (Fox West Coast), Glendale (Folder 213)
  - Carlos Theatre (Peninsula Theatre Corp.), San Carlos (Folder 213)
  - Carv-Arts (Folder 311)
  - Central Theatre (Pacific Amusement), Los Angeles (Folder 213)
  - Chapultepec Theatre, Mexico City (Folder 214)
  - Charisse Dance School (Folder 268)
  - Christman (Walt) - [Walt's Bicycle Shop] Store and Apartment, Los Angeles (Folder 268)
  - Cinema Theatre, Los Angeles (Folder 214)
  - Cohen (Benjamin E.) - Hotel, Chicago (Folder 269)
  - Cohen (M.M.) -residence, Los Angeles (Folder 155)
  - Coliseum Theatre, San Francisco (Folder 214)
  - Copeland (J.I.) - residence, Los Angeles (Folder 155)
  - Cowhick (Oscar) - Store Building (Folder 269)
  - Daniels (Mary) - Store, Los Angeles (Folder 269)
  - Danziger (Ed) - residence, Beverly Hills or Highland Hills (Folder 156)
  - Darby Co. Factory, Inglewood (Folder 269)
  - Davis residence, Monrovia (Folder 157)
  - De Anza Theatre (Hunt's Theatres Inc.), Riverside (Folder 248)
  - Dell'aqua (Mario) - houses, San Diego (Folder 157)
  - DeMille's (Cecil B.) - Store Building, Los Angeles (Folder 269)
  - Dinuba Theatre (Dinuba Theatre Co.), Dinuba (Folder 215)
  - Drive-in Theatre ([Edwards (J.) Jr.]), Arcadia (Folder 216)
  - Du Barry Apartments - Kalb (J.) apartment building, Los Angeles (Folder 165)
  - Easterday Supply Co. Building, Los Angeles (Folder 271)
  - El Capitan Theatre, Mexico (Folder 217)
  - El Capitan Theatre (Fox West Coast), San Francisco (Folder 216)
  - Epstein (Helen) - Building, Hollywood (Folder 272)
  - Esnard (Paul F.) - Professional Building, Los Angeles (Folder 272)
  - F H A duplex (Folder 157)
  - F H A houses (Folder 157)
  - F H A residence, San Bernadino (Folder 157)
  - Factory (unidentified), Los Angeles (Folder 272)
  - Fairfax Storage - Jacobs (Carl E.) (Folder 279)
  - Fairview Manor Apartment building, Reno (Folder 157)
  - Feingold (Ben) - residence (Folder 157)
  - Feldman (Charles K.) - beach bungalow (Folder 157)
  - Feldman (Phillip) - apartment building (Folder 157)
  - Fifth Church of Christ Scientist Reading and sales room (Folder 202)
  - Finks (Frank) Store, [Hollywood] (Folder 272)
  - First Baptist Church, Hollywood (Folder 142)
  - Fiske (R.W.) - residence, Altadena (Folder 158)
  - Fordonia Building, Reno (Folder 272)
  - Fox California Theatre (Fox West Coast), San Diego (Folder 216)
  - Fox Florence Theatre (Fox West Coast), Los Angeles (Folder 218)
  - Fox Long Beach Theatre (Fox Deluxe), Long Beach (Folder 243)
  - Fox Long Beach Theatre (Fox Deluxe), Long Beach (Folder 243)
  - Fox Phoenix Theatre (Fox West Coast), Phoenix (Folder 194)
  - Fox Phoenix Theatre (Fox West Coast), Phoenix (Folder 219)
  - Fox Theatre (Bakersfield Auto Supply), Bakersfield (Folder 220)
  - Fox Theatre (Fox West Coast /[Bershon (D.)]), Los Angeles (Folder 245)
  - Fox Theatre (Fox West Coast), Bell (Folder 244)
  - Fox Theatre (Fox West Coast), Glendale (Folder 244)
  - Fox Theatre (Fox West Coast), Los Angeles (Folder 244)
  - Fox Theatre (Fox West Coast), San Pablo (Folder 246)
  - Fox Theatre (Fox West Coast/ [Berson (D.)]), Los Angeles (Folder 245)
  - Fox West Coast (Loew's State Theatre), Los Angeles (Folder 229)
  - Fox West Coast Commissary (Folder 273)
  - Fox West Coast Stores (Tower Theatres), Compton (Folder 273)
  - Fox West Coast Theatre, Anaheim (Folder 215)
  - Fox Westwood [Bruin] (Fox Westwood Realty), Los Angeles (Folder 215)
  - Fox Wilshire Theatre (Pacific Amusement), Beverly Hills (Folder 221)
  - Franks (Abraham J.) - Mausoleum, Chicago (Folder 202)
  - Fransson & Crane residence (Folder 158)
  - Fremont Theatre (San Luis Obispo Theatres), San Luis Obispo (Folder 222)
  - Fresno Theatre (Fresno Theatres Inc.), Fresno (Folder 247)
  - Fudge (Fred) - (Chrysler Showroom) Building, Huntington Park (Folder 273)
  - Garmar Theatre - Olander (Alfred), Montebello (Folder 222)
  - General Petroleum Corporation Service Station (Folder 273)
  - General Water Heater Building (Folder 274)
  - Glass (Samuel) - apartment building, Redondo Beach (Folder 158)
  - Glatt (William) - residence, Los Angeles (Folder 158)
  - Globe Department Store, Inglewood (Folder 274)
  - Globe Department Store, Los Angeles (Folder 274)
  - Godissart Co. Store, Santa Monica (Folder 275)
  - Godissart Co. Store (Loew's State Theatre), Los Angeles (Folder 275)
  - Goldenburg (H.) - residence, Altadena (Folder 158)
  - Grand Lake Theatre (Fox West Coast), Oakland (Folder 222)
  - Gray (Alexander) - Residence, Beverly Hills (Folder 158)
  - Greek Orthodox Church (Folder 191)
  - Greek Orthodox Church, Los Angeles (Folder 203)
  - Greene & Hinkle Store, Beverly Hills (Folder 275)
  - Haddon Hall (Oberndorf Brothers) - apartment building, Los Angeles (Folder 172)
  - Halper-Robbin residence, Los Angeles (Folder 158)
  - Hartley (J.F.) - residence (Folder 159)
  - Harwin's Jewelers Store, San Pedro (Folder 277)
  - Harwin's Jewelry Store - Horwitz (Carl), Inglewood (Folder 279)
  - Hayden (Sam) -(Lanai House), Beverly Hills (Folder 159)
  - Hayden Lee (Building 110) (Folder 144)
  - Hayden Lee Corp. Factory for Lee Tex Rubber Plant, Los Angeles (Folder 144)
  - Hayden Lee Corporation factory for Blisscraft of Hollywood (Bldg. 112), Gardena (Folder 144)
  - Hayden Lee Corporation Factory for C.E. Duggan & Sons, Los Angeles (Folder 144)
  - Hayden Lee Factor for Hollypark-Crenshaw Co. (Folder 145)
  - Heinsbergen residence (Folder 159)
  - Heinsbergen residence (Folder 189)
  - Helix Theatre (Burton I. Jones), La Mesa (Folder 223)
  - Hermosa Beach Theatre (Fox West Coast), Hermosa Beach (Folder 224)
  - Hickey (George) - Residence (Folder 160)
  - Hickey (George) - Residence (Folder 310)
  - Hillcrest Country Club Clubhouse (Folder 277)
  - Hilton E.G.-Auto Showroom Building, Huntington Park (Folder 278)
  - Hollywood & Vine Corporation (Melody Lane) Restaurant, Hollywood (Folder 279)
  - Hollywood State Bank, Hollywood (Folder 279)
  - Hollywood-Western Building (Mayer Investment), Hollywood (Folder 190)
  - Hollywood-Western Building (Mayer Investment), Hollywood (Folder 291)
    1928 (FRAGILE)
  - Hopkins Theatre - Goldsmith (Laurence), Oakland (Folder 224)
  - Hotel del Tahquitz - Thomas P. Lipps Hotel, Palm Springs (Folder 284)
  - Houston (W.W.) - Factory (Folder 279)
  - Hughes Aircraft Corporation, Los Angeles (Folder 146)
  - Hungerford (Leo) - residence, Los Angeles (Folder 161)
  - Hunt (Phillip) - residence, Los Angeles (Folder 162)
  - Hunt (Phillip) - residence, Los Angeles (Folder 162)
  - Hunter (C. Roy) - cottages, Indio (Folder 162)
  - Huntington Park Theatres, Bell (Folder 248)
  - Huntridge Theatre (Huntridge Development Co.), Las Vegas (Folder 225)
  - Inglewood Theatre (Beaver & Matson), Inglewood (Folder 225)
  - International Investment apartment building, Los Angeles (Folder 163)
  - Inyokern Project (Folder 146)
  - Jacobs (M.) Jr. - residence, Los Angeles (Folder 164)
  - Jassby (N.) - residence (Folder 164)
  - Johnson (Art) - Beauty Parlor (Folder 280)
  - Kaplan & Greenberg fourplex, Los Angeles (Folder 166)
  - Karl's Shoe Store, Los Angeles (Folder 280)
  - Kass & Ruben apartment building, Los Angeles (Folder 166)
  - Kass & Ruben bungalows, Pine Valley (Folder 166)
  - Kenmore-Wilshire Hotel, Los Angeles (Folder 280)
  - Kenmore-Wilshire Hotel - Fidelity Holding Co. (Folder 156)
  - Kinema Theatre, Los Angeles (Folder 226)
  - Kozberg (Ed) - residence (Folder 167)
  - L & O Theatres Inc., Alameda (Folder 248)
  - La Quinta Development (Desert Club), La Quinta (Folder 281)
  - La Reina Theatre (Sherman Oaks Theatre Corp.), Sherman Oaks (Folder 226)
  - La Tijera Theatre - Kupper (W.J.), Los Angeles (Folder 227)
  - Lake & Newman Men's Store (Folder 282)
  - Lakeville Corporation Building, Lakewood (Folder 282)
  - Lakewood Theatre (Lakeville Corporation), Lakewood (Folder 228)
  - Laykin et Cie Building, Los Angeles (Folder 282)
  - Leadley (W.S.) Theatre, San Mateo (Folder 249)
  - Leavitt (M.L.) - Building (Folder 282)
  - Lee (Don) Radio Station, Los Angeles (Folder 270)
  - Lee (S. Charles) - duplex, Los Angeles (Folder 167)
  - Lee (S. Charles) - Office, Los Angeles (Folder 283)
  - Lee (S. Charles) - Office Building, Los Angeles (Folder 283)
  - Lee (S. Charles) - residence, Los Angeles (Folder 167)
  - Lee (S. Charles) and Jones (Burton) - Commercial Store Bldg., Reseda (Folder 146)
  - Leehal Inc. Housing (Folder 168)
  - Leimert (Walter H.) Co. - (Plaza Professional Building), Los Angeles (Folder 283)
  - LeRoy Diamond Co. Store (Folder 282)
  - Levin (D.B.) - residence, San Mateo (Folder 168)
  - Levy (B.) Store / Apartment Building, Los Angeles (Folder 283)
  - Linda Vista Theatre, Tepeyac, Mexico (Folder 238)
  - Loma Theatre (Balboa Building Co.), San Diego (Folder 229)
  - Long Beach Packard Building, Long Beach (Folder 285)
  - Los Angeles Theatre (H.L. Gumbiner), Los Angeles (Folder 230)
  - Los Prados Apartments (Folder 147)
  - Lyceum Theatre, San Francisco (Folder 229)
  - Lyons (et al) Store Building, Hollywood (Folder 285)
  - MacLean (Robert) - residence (Folder 169)
  - MacPherson (Granville) Theatre, Yerington, Nevada (Folder 250)
  - Malinow & Simmons Chapel (Folder 204)
  - Malsman (S.) Burton & Co. - Store Building, Los Angeles (Folder 286)
  - Manchester Theatre (Southside Theatres), Los Angeles (Folder 231)
  - March (Frederick) - residence (Projection Room) (Folder 170)
  - Marshall (Thomas F.) Store (Folder 286)
  - Max Factor building (Folder 190)
  - Max Factor Building, Hollywood (Folder 287)
    #314, #320 - Additions and Alterations; see sheet #8 Highland Ave. Elevation - Arch.
  - Max Factor Building, Hollywood (Folder 288)
    #331, #467, #345, #351, #352 - Arch./Details, Schedules (Specs), Seismic calcs, interiors
  - Max Factor Building, Hollywood (Folder 289)
    #351, #331, #331A, #467B - Structurals, seismic, architecturals (some), schemes A & B, mechanical (some), signage, concept sketches (many)
  - Max Factor Store and Office Building, Hollywood (Folder 290)
    #331A - 6781 Hawthorne Ave. (Addition between Wilshire and Hawthorne; also includes 3 sheets details, 10 sheets structurals for 1666 N. Highland.
  - Max Factor Studio, London (Folder 290)
  - Mayer (Louis B.) - Store, Los Angeles (Folder 292)
  - Mayfair Theatre - Dodge (J.), Ventura (Folder 193)
  - Mayfair Theatre - Dodge (J.), Ventura (Folder 231)
  - McGee (A.E.) - residence (Folder 170)
  - McGhee (George) - apartment building, Los Angeles (Folder 170)
  - Metzger (Lou) - residence (Bomb Shelter), Bel Air (Folder 170)
  - Meyer (W.) - apartment building, Los Angeles (Folder 171)
  - Miami Theatre (Wometco), Miami (Folder 232)
  - Mier (Harry) - residence (Folder 171)
  - Millman (M.) - Medical Office Building (Folder 292)
  - Miracle Mile Plot Plan, Los Angeles (Folder 148)
  - Monahan (Frank) Building, Los Angeles (Folder 292)
  - Morgan (C.C.) & King (L.B.) - housing development, Sunland (Folder 171)
  - Morrison residence (Folder 171)
  - Moss (Hilda) - store buildings, Van Nuys (Folder 146)
  - Mount Sinai Clinic (Folder 204)
  - Municipal Light Water and Power Building, Los Angeles (Folder 141)
  - Municipal Light Water and Power Building, Los Angeles (Folder 293)
  - National Missile & Electronics (Joel Moss Bldg.), Los Angeles (Folder 147)
  - Newsreel (Diana) Theatre (Folder 193)
  - Nor-Ten Corporation Building (Folder 294)
  - Norton Brothers & Morris Building (Folder 294)
  - Oldknow Oscar-residence, Bel Air (Folder 173)
  - Pacht Isaac-residence, Los Angeles (Folder 174)
  - Pantages Theatre, Los Angeles (Folder 250)
  - Pavlow (Alex) Theatre, Los Angeles (Folder 250)
  - Peterson Carl H.-apartment building, Fresno (Folder 175)
  - Picwood Theatre (Earl Collins), Los Angeles (Folder 233)
  - Piltzer (D.) - Store Building, Los Angeles (Folder 294)
  - Polytechnic College Beauty Shop, Los Angeles (Folder 295)
  - Prosperity Klub (Folder 142)
  - Prosperity Klub (Folder 295)
  - Radio Bar Interior - Lyon (M.L.), Los Angeles (Folder 285)
  - Ralph's Grocery Co. Market, Los Angeles (Folder 295)
  - Redondo Theatre (Redondo Properties), Redondo Beach (Folder 234)
  - Redwood Theatres Inc., Modesto (Folder 251)
  - Redwood Theatres Inc. - Theatre #2, Woodland (Folder 252)
  - Reseda Theatre - Grenzbach (Charles), Reseda (Folder 234)
  - Reynard Hills - San Diego Alpha Corporation Development - site analysis, San Diego (Folder 148)
  - Rialto Theatre - Becchetti (Frank), Cottonwood, Arizona (Folder 242)
  - Ritz Theatre (Folder 195)
  - Rivoli Theatre (Folder 195)
  - Rivoli Theatre, Van Nuys (Folder 235)
  - Rivoli Theatre sign (Folder 188)
  - Roberts (C.P.) - residence (Folder 177)
  - Robinson (Louis) Medical Building, Beverly Hills (Folder 296)
  - Robinson (S.A.) - residence, Los Angeles (Folder 177)
  - Rogers (Martha) and Squires (Ella) - Building, Los Angeles (Folder 296)
  - Rosemead Theatre (Edwards Theatres), Rosemead (Folder 235)
  - Rosen (E.M.) - Market, Pasadena (Folder 297)
  - Roxie Theatre (Srere & Metzger), Los Angeles (Folder 235)
  - Rusinow (Sidney) - Building (Folder 297)
  - Russel (J.S.) - Market, Los Angeles (Folder 297)
  - Russell (D.A.) & Reinger (Grace) - Store and Apartment Building, Los Angeles (Folder 297)
  - Sanford-Jacobi Store Building, Hollywood (Folder 298)
  - Scheinman (Benjamin) - residence (Folder 178)
  - Schwab Inyokern Stores, Inyokern (Folder 298)
  - Schwab's Store Building - Schwab (Dore), Hollywood (Folder 298)
  - Seelee Theatre Co., Selma (Folder 254)
  - Seigelman (William H.) - apartment building, Los Angeles (Folder 178)
  - Senator Theatre (Fox West Coast), Oakland (Folder 236)
  - Senior Examination Boards (Folder 143)
  - Sheehan (Howard) - apartment (Fox-Wilshire Theatre Building), Beverly Hills (Folder 178)
  - Sherman (J.W.) - residence, Los Angeles (Folder 178)
  - Shirley Corporation apartment building, Beverly Hills (Folder 179)
  - Sierra Theatre - Panero (Frank), Delano (Folder 250)
  - Silbert & Lee apartment building (Folder 180)
  - Silbert (Sam) - residence, Los Angeles (Folder 180)
  - Silbert apartment building (Folder 180)
  - Simmonds (J.) - Store, Los Angeles (Folder 299)
  - Simon (Sylvan) - residence, Beverly Hills (Folder 181)
  - Sims (Herman) - residence, Los Angeles (Folder 181)
  - Skouras (Charles P.) - Office Suite (Folder 299)
  - Skouras (Charles P.) - residence, New York (Folder 182)
  - Skouras (Charles P.) - residence, Beverly Hills (Folder 182)
  - Skouras residence, Beverly Hills (Folder 189)
  - Skouras Theatre, New York (Folder 241)
  - Smith & White Bowling Alley (Folder 299)
  - Sontag Drug Co. Building, Los Angeles (Folder 300)
  - St. Clair (Edward) - residence (Folder 183)
  - Staber's Store Building (Dr. Barton) (Folder 266)
  - State Theatre (Fox West Coast), Stockton (Folder 236)
  - State Theatre (Fox West Coast), San Diego (Folder 236)
  - Stern (William) - residence, Los Angeles (Folder 183)
  - Stevens Shops (Stevens Store), Portland, Oregon (Folder 301)
  - Stevens Shops Inc. Store Building, Long Beach (Folder 301)
  - Stevens Stores (Stevens Store), Los Angeles (Folder 301)
  - Stinson Airplane Sales Office Building, Glendale (Folder 302)
  - Studio Theatre (Hughes Franklin, Inc.), Hollywood (Folder 237)
  - Sunbeam Theatre Co. (Folder 254)
  - Syers & Richardson Restaurant (Folder 302)
  - Theatre, Los Angeles (Folder 240)
  - Theatre, Las Vegas (Folder 240)
  - Theatre / Apartment (Folder 240)
  - Theatre / Apartments, Redlands (Folder 241)
  - Theatre interior (Folder 188)
  - Theatres (Folder 308)
  - Theatres (Folder 309)
  - Theatres (black and white sketches) (Folder 196)
  - Theatres (black and white sketches) (Folder 197)
  - Theatres (black and white sketches) (Folder 198)
  - Theatres (black and white sketches) (Folder 199)
  - Theatres (color sketches) (Folder 200)
  - Thompson (Earle) - tore Building, Glendale (Folder 302)
  - Thompson (Rose & Annie) - Warehouse, Los Angeles (Folder 302)
  - Tipp (Dave) - Shops, Los Angeles (Folder 303)
  - Tower Bowl, San Diego (Folder 190)
  - Tower Bowl Bowling Alley - Hanson (A.J.), San Diego (Folder 276)
  - Tower Theatre, San Diego (Folder 188)
  - Tower Theatre, Los Angeles (Folder 188)
  - Tower Theatre (H.L. Gumbiner), Los Angeles (Folder 258)
  - Tower Theatre (H.L. Gumbiner), Los Angeles (Folder 259)
  - Tower Theatre (Metzger & Srere), San Diego (Folder 260)
  - Tower Theatre (Rosenberg), Santa Rosa (Folder 253)
  - Tower Theatre (West Coast Compton Theatres), Compton (Folder 257)
  - Toys Theatre, Helena, Montana (Folder 261)
  - Trabert & Hoeffer Store, Los Angeles (Folder 303)
  - Trabue-Pittman Corporation Market & Store Building, Los Angeles (Folder 304)
  - Troyer (J. Vance) - (Melrose Hotel / Apartments) (Folder 304)
  - Troyer Bros. apartment building (Folder 183)
  - Troyer Bros. apartment building (Folder 183)
  - Tujunga Theatre (Edwards), Tujunga (Folder 261)
  - Tumbleweed Theatre (Edwards Theatre Circuit) Five Points, [El Monte] (Folder 262)
  - Ullman (Frank) Theatre [State?], San Diego (Folder 255)
  - Unidentified (Folder 143)
  - Unidentified - Dining Room (Folder 148)
  - Unidentified Apartment building, Los Angeles (Folder 149)
  - Unidentified Apartment building, Glendale (Folder 149)
  - Unidentified Apartment building, Los Angeles (Folder 149)
  - Unidentified building, Huntington Park (Folder 268)
  - Unidentified bungalow (Folder 153)
  - Unidentified Commercial Building (Folder 311)
  - Unidentified Hotel (Folder 312)
  - Unidentified Houses (Folder 161)
  - Unidentified Market (Folder 312)
  - Unidentified Office forms (Folder 191)
  - Unidentified Offices (Folder 141)
    includes Wurlitzer and L.A. Water and Power
  - Unidentified Residence, Beverly Hills (Folder 177)
  - Unidentified Residence (Folder 310)
  - Unidentified Residences (Folder 176)
    (one FRAGILE)
  - Unidentified Sales Office (Folder 298)
  - Unidentified Shops, Modesto (Folder 298)
  - Unidentified Shops, Las Vegas (Folder 298)
  - Unidentified Store Building, Sherman Oaks (Folder 302)
  - Unidentified Store near Ventura (Folder 302)
  - Unidentified Theatre (Folder 240)
  - Unidentified Theatre, Los Angeles (Folder 240)
  - Unidentified Theatres (Folder 239)
  - Unidentified Tourist Cabins (Folder 303)
  - Union Furniture, San Francisco (Folder 190)
  - Union Furniture Co. Store, San Francisco (Folder 305)
  - United States Engineers Office, Los Angeles (Folder 205)
  - United Verde Copper Theatre, Clarkdale, Arizona (Folder 255)
  - Universal Holding Company apartment building, Los Angeles (Folder 184)
  - Universal Holding Company Duplex 10, Los Angeles (Folder 184)
  - Universal Holding Company Duplex 11, Los Angeles (Folder 185)
  - Universal Holding Company Duplex 12, Los Angeles (Folder 185)
  - Universal Holding Company Duplex 13, Los Angeles (Folder 185)
  - Universal Holding Company Duplex 14, Los Angeles (Folder 185)
  - Universal Holding Company Duplex 15, Los Angeles (Folder 186)
  - Universal Holding Company Duplex 16, Los Angeles (Folder 186)
  - Universal Holding Company Duplex 2, Los Angeles (Folder 184)
  - Universal Holding Company Duplex 6, Los Angeles (Folder 184)
  - Universal Holding Company Duplex 7, Los Angeles (Folder 184)
  - Universal Holding Company Duplex 8, Los Angeles (Folder 184)
  - Universal Holding Company Duplex 9, Los Angeles (Folder 184)
  - Valley Theatre [Weddington (Guy)], North Hollywood (Folder 262)
  - Variety Club (Premature Clinic, Cedars of Lebanon Children's Hospital), Los Angeles (Folder 205)
  - Vaughan McCarit Evans Corporation Office, Los Angeles (Folder 306)
  - Verdi Theatre, San Francisco (Folder 263)
  - Vern Theatre (Wyvernwood Theatres, Inc.), Los Angeles (Folder 263)